thegamepod.com 2016-10-20

# Privacy Policy | TheGamePod

Privacy Policy

TheGamePod is committed to protecting your information and privacy. We describe what information we collect from you and how we share and utilize such information in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy governs the use of our site, www.TheGamePod.com (referred to as “Site”) and our online gaming application (“Software”). This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into our End User License Agreement (referred to as our “EULA”).

Section 1. Changes to this Policy

We may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time at anytime of our choosing, so be sure to check back periodically. If we make any changes to this Privacy Policy that materially affect our internal practices and/or safety measures with regard to the personally identifiable information that we have previously collected from you, we will update this Privacy Policy so that it reflects the current stat of collection procedures.

Section 2. Installing the Software

Once you download and install our Software, as discussed below, we will collect information about you, including, your browser activity, the URLs you visit, and the web content on such visited URLs.

Section 3. Ads from the Software

Our Software contain advertisements, such as video, textlink, interstitial and pop-ups. Some of such advertisements are targeted for you based on your particular visit to a website on your general online browsing behaviour while other advertisements are displayed based on aggregate criteria, independent of your online usage behaviour. We use commercially reasonable efforts to provide advertising that we think is relevant to you and advertising that we think might catch your interest and attention. To provide you with such targeted advertisements, we examine your online usage activity (such as, browser activity, pages you visit, etc.). This enables us to provide you with customized advertisements and allows us to maintain the premium games you play on our Site as a free service.

Section 4. Opting out of Advertisements

The users is not required to receive all advertisements from the Software in order to enjoy the premium games on the Sites. Some advertisements allow the user to disable such advertisements, such that disable instructions are provided from a link located in the unit of advertisement. However, the Software must be uninstalled if you would like to stop receiving all advertisements from the Software. For instructions on how to uninstall the Software, please go to the Uninstall section of the EULA. Please email us at customercontact@TheGamePod.com if you have any questions.

Section 5. Information We collect About You

We collect information about you in various ways, including, information that we collect from you directly when you send us an email with your questions; information we collect about you when you visit the Site; and information we collect about you through our Software. All such information is collected anonymously for purposes of maintaining and improving our overall services all the while keeping it free of charge.

Information We Collect When you Visit the Site: We use web beacons, cookies and other tracking technologies to collect information about you when you visit the Site. Specifically, we collect your browser type, IP address, operating system, date and time of your visit to the Site, time spent on the Site, any mechanism by which you can to the Site and links clicked on the Site.

Section 6. How We Use the Collected Information

We use the information that we collect about you for the following purposes:

· To provide our products and services (such as premium games) to you free of charge;

· To make our premium products and services to you;

· To Improve the Site and Software, such as trouble shooting technical issues, maintaining, its operation and creating updates;

· For research purposes; and

· To serve more targeted advertisements based on the user’s web browsing activity.

Section 7. How We Share the Collected Information

We may share your non-personally identifiable information (collectively, “NPII”), that we collect about you to provision the products and services that you request, to comply with the legal process, to provide targeted advertisements to you and for other purposes as described in this section. We also share your information for the following proposes explained below, which may include sharing with our third party merchant affiliates, business partners and other third party person or entities.

To Perform Certain Services on Our Behalf. We may hire third party vendor companies to perform services on our behalf, such as providing technical assistance, sending electronic mail, to provide database analysis and to assist us in providing the products and services that you request from us. We only provide such third party service providers with the information necessary to perform their requested service.

To Protect our company and for legal purpose. We also may disclose your information to prevent against fraud and abuse, to protect our rights and property to protect the user of our Site and Software. We also may disclose your information as permitted or required by law or a governmental authority (for example, in response to subpoenas, court orders or other requests for information from such entities).

Sale/Transfer of Business. If we are merged with or acquired by another company, and if all or substantially all our assets are transferred to such company, or as part of a bankruptcy proceeding, we may transfer the information we have collected from you to the acquiring company.

Anonymized and Aggregate Information. We may share anonymized or aggregate information about our users with third parties for advertising, marketing, research or similar purposes. For example, if we display third party advertisements on a third party’s behalf, we may share aggregate, demographic information with that third party about the users to whom such advertisements were displayed.

Section 8. How Do We Use Cookies & Other Tracking Technologies?

When we interact with the Site, we strive to make your experience convenient and meaningful. We may use or engage others to use cookies, clear gifs, and flash track your activity and collect data via the Site. We may combine this data with other information we collect from you. We use cookie data to recognize you as a particular user when you visit the Site, to aggregate user traffic flow and to aid our Site’s features and functionalities.

Cookies. When you visit the Site, our web server places a cookie on your computer. Cookies are small fields that can be sued as record-keeping identifiers that we place onto your computer’s hard drive through via our Site. There are session-based cookies and persistent-based cookies. In addition, we also may permit certain third party cookies to be placed on the Site as well.

Session Cookies. Sessions cookies exist only during your online sessions with the Site. Session Cookies automatically disappear from your computer when your browser is closed or when your computer is turned off. We use session cookies to allow our systems to uniquely identify you as a user while you are using the Site. This allow us to process your online transactions and requests and also to verify your user identify, as you Move through our Site.

Persistent Cookies. Persistent cookies remain on your computer after your browser is closed and your computer is turned off. We may use persistent cookies to track aggregate and statistical information about your online activity, which may be combined with other user information as well.

Third Party Cookies. We also may engage with third parties in order to track and analyse non-personally identifiable information in the form of Site data. We use the data collected by such third parties to help us administer and improve the quality of the Site and to analyse usage statistics. We do not have access to or control over such third party cookies nor dos this Privacy Policy cover such third parties’ use of such data.

Disabling Cookies. Most web browsers will automatically accept cookies. However, if you prefer to block cookies, you may do so by selecting the appropriate cookie disabling action in your web browser settings. The Settings or Help portion of the menu bard on most browsers will provide instructions on how to prevent our computer from accepting new cookies, how to notify you via the browser when you receive a new cookie and/or how to disable cookies altogether.

Clear Gifs (aka Web Beacons and/or Web Bugs). We (or the third parties) may also engage to track and analyse Site data by employing clear gifs (e.g. Web Beacons and/or Web Bugs) to help us better manage content on the Site. Clear gifs are small graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to that of cookies, and are used to track online movements of users on the Site. As opposed to cookies, which are stored on your computer, clear gifs are invisibly embedded on the Site.

Section 9. Security of Information

We have implemented commercially reasonable precautions, including, where appropriate, password protection, encryption, and SSL to protect our Site and the information we collect form loss, misuse, and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration and destruction. Please be aware that despite our best efforts, no data security measures can guarantee 100% security all of the time.

Section 10. Children Under 13

Neither our Site nor our Software is intended to be used or accessed by children under 13 years old. We do not knowingly collect personal information form children under 13, but if we unintentionally do, please notify us immediately at [customercontact@TheGamePod.com](mailto:customercontact@TheGamePod.com) and we will immediately remove such information from our database.

Section 11. How to Contact Us

If you have questions about this Privacy Policy or about any of our information collection practices, please do not hesitate to email us at [customercontact@TheGamePod.com](mailto:customercontact@TheGamePod.com).
